So we created a context, we have grabbed our application with ultraviolet.
So let's go ahead and give it a try.
Let's create a new screen home screen.
And it's create a basic component here, so important we are going to start using context, we need
to use the use context to it's important as well.
Let's import some components.
Text and the view from React native included input takes from cholera and just the native view from
React native to import from.
Coloreds react, native text and then we want to import the context Asian, so you need to invert the
use context hook and the context itself, which is out of context from.
So we go one step up, go into context and grab from us.
Okay, so we've got the context as well.
Now let's we can
return.
They may return a view.
Intel view text.
We're going to write something.
Let me just write home for the.
Export default, and let's make sure we import this one and abductees.
Screens.
Let's put it in, Mr.
I'm sorry, something happened.
Change the name to.
Something happened here, I think that duplicated some of that.
OK.
When we got in that, don't done this to come.
That's a screaming and screaming component.
OK, initial round Libya tends to home for now, just so that we can give it a try.
And device sake.
So you can see where home we can barely see that, but it's that it's a home.
So what do you want to do here is I want to try accessing the context state so that we can use, we
can destruction, so we want to get the access to state, said State.
That's from the context, right?
So do you that we can use use context and give us context?
Perfect.
No.
You can actually try having a look at the context state and you can also be listed.
So let's have look do some string, if I may ask you to put it into text so this country for state know
for.
Let's make sure we wrap everything in time coded risk because this is our school and that is also where
you can see here we have got the user and funding from the state.
How great is that?
Now you can see this global state can be accessed on any components just like this one.
You need to introduce context to import of context.
And you can access the global state and of the global state like this on any component in any schools?